{
  "questions": {
    "multiQuestions": [
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is a Family Type?",
        "answer": "Instance types that have similar hardware specifications (CPU, vRAM, etc)",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is a security group?",
        "answer": "An instance level firewall allowing you to restrict Ingress and Egress traffic by specifying what traffic is allowed to communicate with that instance",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What are some options of a Security Group to restrict inbound and outbound communication to an EC2 instance?",
        "answer": "Source, Ports, and Protocols",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What protocols are supported by ALB?",
        "answer": "HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, SMTP, and NFS",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "TCP, TLS, UDP, TCP_UDP"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What protocols are supported by NLB?",
        "answer": "TCP, TLS, UDP, TCP_UDP",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, SMTP, and NFS"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "Elastic Load Balancer (ELB) balances traffic to a(n)",
        "answer": "Target Group",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "AutoScaling Group"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "EC2 Auto Scaling scales instances inside of a(n)",
        "answer": "AutoScaling Group",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "Target Group"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "When ALB uses HTTPS, what is the type of server certificate used?",
        "answer": "X.509 certificate",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "X.510 certificate",
          "X.409 certificate",
          "X.601 certificate"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is Cross-Zone Load Balancing?",
        "answer": "A setting for ELB. When enabled, ELBs will distribute traffic to targets across AZs evenly",
        "wrongAnswers": [
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "For Lambda, which policy determines what resources the function has access to while running?",
        "answer": "Role Excecution Policies",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "Function Policy"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "For Lambda, which policy determines which AWS resources are allowed to invoke your function?",
        "answer": "Function Policy",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "Role Excecution Policies"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "booleanQuestions": [
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "If an EC2 instance is stopped, ephemoral storage is lost",
        "answer": "True",
        "popup": "",
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "If an EC2 instance is rebooted, ephemoral storage is lost",
        "answer": "False",
        "popup": "",
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "By default, AWS Lambda encrypts your environment variables *after* the function has been deployed",
        "answer": "True",
        "popup": "",
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "checkboxQuestions": [
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What are some options to get an AMI (Amazon Machine Image)?",
        "answers": [
          "Create your own",
          "AWS Marketplace",
          "Community AMIs"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What are the different GLB types?",
        "answers": [
          "ALB",
          "NLB",
          "Classic Load Balancer"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "Name the different Family Types",
        "answers": [
          "Micro Instances",
          "General Purpose",
          "Compute Optimized",
          "GPU Instances",
          "FPGA Instances",
          "Memory Optimized",
          "Storage Optimized"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "Which of these are some Instance Purchasing Options?",
        "answers": [
          "On-Demand Instances",
          "Reserved Instances",
          "Scheduled Instances",
          "Spot Instances",
          "On-Demand Capacity Reservations"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
}